Iterator under construction

--In Simple List class, there is a function named operator bool() that takes in no argument. What does it do?

-- In Simple List class, one of the member functions, T Delete, calls Iterator to delete iMarker. Does the return delete_head pass in iMarker or head_ptr?

--In Simple List class, what does the member access operator (the arrow) return? Pointer?

--In light of the last question, go to your stack class. What does your top() return? Originally I called stack.Begin()-->_item. Does it stay the same? 

--In stack class, my pop's assert calls Iterator p.is_null is !true. Is this correct?